Theodoros Georgakopoulos

Computer Engineer

Email: tgeorgako@gmail.com

Web: tgeorgako.github.io/

CV in PDF: https://tgeorgako.github.io/resume.pdf

About Me

Hi, my name is Theodoros Georgakopoulos and I am a computer engineer. I enjoy building and troubleshooting systems and creating applications. Throughout my career I have worked at many companies and institutions gaining teamwork and leadership skills.

I am most skilled in building websites and handling complicated IT problems.

Education

University of Patras Diploma, Department of Computer Engineering & Informatics

The Computer Engineering & Informatics Department (CEID) of the Engineering School of the University of Patras was founded in 1979. The department's mission is to provide education and research in the broad field of Computer Science and Engineering (CS&E), Communications and Informatics.

During my time at CEID I learnt most of my key skills that have I have taken through my career such as teamwork and working to tight deadlines. During my student years, I have successfully completed a number of projects while developing my skills.

University of Patras MSc Human-Computer Interaction

2019 - Present

The objective of the Masters Program is to provide specialized theoretical and applied knowledge on concepts related to the study, design and development of interactive technologies, i.e. technologies that interact with their users, as well as the study of phenomena related to interaction of users with modern technologies.

1

Foreign Languages

English Level C2

Certificate of Proficiency in English (ECPE), University of Michigan

French Level B2

DELF 1er degré (UNITES A1, A2, A3, A4)

Experience

Municipality of Kalavryta IT specialist

2018 - Present

IT support, network administration and customer support.

Phonedoctor.gr Phonedoctor.gr

Computer hardware repair technician

2014 - Present

IT support in computer and network systems, cell phones

e-socials.gr e-socials.gr

Web developer

2016 - 2018

Web design and management, social media and web advertising.

Hlektroniki Riou Computer hardware repair technician

2013 - 2017

IT support in computer and network systems, CCTV and alarm security, satellite and digital TV.

OTE, Hellenic Telecommunications Organisation S.A. Telephone Service Representative

2008 - 2009

Customer service, IT support

Skills

- Excellent use and support of operating systems, office applications and services (MS Windows, Linux, MacOS, MS Office).
- Digital Marketing (Google Adwords, Business Facebook).
- Excellent use and configuration of smartphone software iOS, Android, Windows Mobile.
- Technical support for computers and mobile systems telephones, closed surveillance systems, telephony.
- Programming knowledge (PHP, Javascipt, Java, Matlab).
- Communication and teamwork skills
- Website Design and Management (Plesk, Wordpress, HTML5, CSS, Javascript, MySQL)
- Driving licence B

Theodoros Georgakopoulos - tgeorgako@gmail.com - References on request